https://www.creationsrewards.net/privacy-policy

Promo Code
Earn points for submitting a valid promo code. We hide them in our website, on social media, and more! Submit a code you found below.
Login
My Account Earning History Shopping History My Referrals Reward History My Profile Logout
Earn Points
Home Watch Videos Take Surveys Explore Websites Discover OfferWalls Listen to Radio Refer Friends Shop
Redeem Points
Redeem CR Points
Daily To-Do List
Login to access this feature.
Win Points
Daily Trivia Game CR Promo Code
My Account
My Account Earning History Shopping History My Referrals Reward History My Profile Logout
Learning Center
Learn CR How to Earn Common Questions Test Yourself Bonus for Learning
Security
CreationsRewards takes every action to protect members information.
We require you to set a password to access your data on our website, and offer you the ability to login every time you visit the website.
We protect your data offline as well.
CreationsRewards employees are only given access to personal data to handle a customer care inquiry or redemption.
Otherwise, employees are not permitted to access personal data on members. CreationsRewards servers are also maintained in a secure and professional environment.
Updating Information
CreationsRewards members can update their personal information at any time by logging into CreationsRewards.Net and clicking on the My
Account link at the top of any page. In this area, members can access the Update Account Information link to make changes to their information, such as E-Mail address or mailing address.
In order to verify the identity of a member, the member will need to enter in their CreationsRewards.Net account password to validate the update request.
Members can also manually E-Mail account updates to the customer care team at helpdesk (at) creationsrewards.net.
Contacting CreationsRewards
CreationsRewards can be contacted via E-Mail at helpdesk (at) creationsrewards.net or by postal mail at:
CreationsRewards.Net118 S. 19th Ave.Manville, NJ 08835
Privacy Policy Effective: May 2011
Home
Home
Take Surveys
Watch & Explore
Download Apps
Shopping
Discover OfferWalls
Redeem Rewards
My Account
Earn Points
Home Watch & Explore Take Surveys Download Apps Discover OfferWalls Refer Friends Shop
Redeem
Redeem CR Points
To-Do List
Login to access this feature.
Win Points
Daily Goal Bonus Daily Trivia Game Scratch Games CR Promo Code
My Account
My Account Earning History Shopping History My Referrals Reward History My Profile Logout
Learn
Take the Tour Learn CR How to Earn Common Questions Test Yourself Bonus for Learning
Social
Facebook
Twitter
HomePrivacy Policy
Paid Online SurveysWe offer many daily surveys that you can complete each day. Visit our Daily Surveys area, and for each survey you complete, you'll earn rewards.
Rewards for Watching VideosLike to watch videos online? Get rewarded for each video you watch in our Videos section. New ones are always being added, so check often!
Get Paid to Try OffersWe partnered with leading advertisers who want you to try their products & services online. Check out our Offer Wall area where you can earn 1000s of points.
Earn cash back for online shopping -- it's like a rebate on each purchase!
Here's some of the stores you can earn cash back at:
Walmart.comJCPenneyBest BuyDunkin Donuts ShopFreeze DefenseMichaelsOffice Depot and OfficeMaxPayless ShoesourceSam's ClubStaplesNewegg.comJoann.comDisneyStore.comPETCO Animal SuppliesPier 1 ImportsVitamin ShoppeWalgreensRiteAidPersonal CreationsHSNBoscov's Department StoreChoice HotelsAutoZone
